

Roman Höhn

B SC BUSINESS EDUCATION

Roedelstueck 26, 55129 Mainz

☐ Mobile: +49 178 4076394 | ☑rohoehn123@gmail.com | ☐roman91DE

About Me

FOCUSSED ON INFORMATION SYSTEMS DURING MY ACADEMIC STUDIES, WITH A PARTICULAR INTEREST FOR EVOLUTIONARY COMPUTATION

SKILLED PROGRAMMER IN PYTHON, C++ AND UNIX SHELL

MANY YEARS OF HANDS-ON EXPERIENCE AS A TEACHER FOR IT AND BUSINESS EDUCATION

Education

Johannes Gutenberg-University

Mainz, Germany

MASTER OF SCIENCE - BUSINESS EDUCATION (MINOR: MANAGEMENT AND ECONOMICS)

2018-2023 (expected)

Johannes Gutenberg-University

Mainz, Germany

2014-2018

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE - BUSINESS EDUCATION (MINOR: UNTERNEHMENSRECHNUNG/CONTROLLING)

Wiesbaden, Germany

OFFICE MANAGEMENT ASSISTANT

A. Panzer GmbH

2012-2014

Martin-Niemöller-Schule

Wiesbaden, Germany

GENERAL HIGHER QUALIFICATION FOR UNIVERSITY ENTRANCE

2007-2010

Berufserfahrung_____

MUT GbR (www.lernfoerderung.de)

Wiesbaden, Deutschland

BUCHHALTUNG UND BETRIEBSWIRTSCHAFTLICHE BERATUNG

seit 2018

Kölner Wirtschaftsfachschule - Wifa-Gruppe - GmbH

Mainz/Darmstadt, Deutschland

FREIBERUFLICHER KAUFMÄNNISCHER FACHDOZENT

2018-2023

Johannes Gutenberg-Universität

Mainz, Deutschland,

WISSENSCHAFTLICHE HILFSKRAFT MIT ABSCHLUSS

2018-2019

Akademische Arbeiten

Pre-Trained Denoising Autoencoders Long Short-Term Memory Networks as probabilistic Models for Estimation of Distribution Genetic Programming

Master Thesis

LEHRSTUHL FÜR WIRTSCHAFTSINFORMATIK UND BWL

https://github.com/roman91DE/master_thesis

Analyzing the influence of Selection on Genetic Programming's Generalization ability in Symbolic Regression: A comparison of epsilon-lexicase Selection and Tournament Selection

Master Seminar

LEHRSTUHL FÜR WIRTSCHAFTSINFORMATIK UND BWL

https://github.com/roman91DE/Analyzingthe-influence-of-Selection-on-Genetic-Programming Trade deflection on Chinese exports of photovoltaic modules and key components as a reaction to the European Union's 2013 anti-dumping duties

Bachelor Thesis

LEHRSTUHL FÜR INTERNATIONAL FINANCE

https://github.com/roman91DE/Bachelor_Thesis